{
    "id": "415acb0ccd254a3dabd788b7083d9604",
    "title": "Irregular Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They ……………………… him to within an inch of his life.",
            "description": "Beat is the past simple of beat.",
            "answers": [
                "beat",
                "beated",
                "bet"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1ee25a7dd2924952bbf9d1a3ea89155f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The welder ……………………………. to his work with determination.",
            "description": "Bent is the past simple of bend.",
            "answers": [
                "bended",
                "bent",
                "bend"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "71909e0dadb1494482ff232644834c2e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Millions of dollars were ………………………… on the Kentucky Derby last year.",
            "description": "Bet is the past simple of bet.",
            "answers": [
                "bet",
                "betted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "619c2ddd84e7489d9c97c64415a34109"
        },
        {
            "question": "The explosion …………………………….. the bridge to smithereens.",
            "description": "Blew is the past simple of blow.",
            "answers": [
                "blowed",
                "blew",
                "blown"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b6815a362db4431d887c6ec76daf2bdd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Last winter, the water pipes ……………………………. in the cold winter.",
            "description": "Burst has only one form – burst.",
            "answers": [
                "bursted",
                "burst",
                "bursed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "312f4af9d6ff4b5d81eb7b3360b8052b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The kids …………………………. a tunnel in the sand.",
            "description": "Dug is the past simple of dig.",
            "answers": [
                "digged",
                "dig",
                "dug"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6cbd0f0c36324ad2b938570efb1bb6c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ………………………….. the drapes.",
            "description": "Drapes are hung.",
            "answers": [
                "hang",
                "hung",
                "hanged"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4815454a93ec461981bf00ed52b6b2cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The terrorist was ………………………….. at dawn.",
            "description": "A human being is hanged.",
            "answers": [
                "hung",
                "hanged",
                "hunged"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2d4c90a7d78d49e8a0ad937945e00a08"
        },
        {
            "question": "They all …………………………. when the king entered.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "knelt",
                "kneeled",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d9e254992262458190ac32842eda24bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "What happened to those ten pounds I …………………………… you?",
            "description": "Lent is the past tense of lend.",
            "answers": [
                "lended",
                "lent"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3d3f3ed8d7fd4a4aa1588dc7f7ea5f80"
        },
        {
            "question": "I must be ………………………… weight.",
            "description": "Losing is the opposite of gaining. ",
            "answers": [
                "loosing",
                "losing",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5b4edc15fcbc424faefed61be55b7fe2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………… down on the couch yesterday.",
            "description": "When lie refers to body position, lay is its past tense. ",
            "answers": [
                "lie",
                "lay",
                "lain"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b925d8bfa1c042e99df853756cda1707"
        }
    ]
}